thenigerialawyer.com 2016-11-27

# Privacy Policy | Thenigerialawyer

[Home](http://thenigerialawyer.com/) Privacy Policy

PRIVACY POLICY:

At **http://thenigerialawyer.com/** , the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected by us and how it is used.  
If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email: **editor@thenigerialawyer.com**

 **LOG FILES:**

Like many other Web sites, <http://thenigerialawyer.com/> makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

 **COOKIES AND WEB BEACONS:**  
[http://thenigerialawyer.com/ ](http://thenigerialawyer.com/)does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.  
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

 **Facebook APP**

This privacy policy applies to content provided by us and your use of the Thenigerialawyers Facebook app (the ‘Thenigerialawyers/’).  
As a registered Facebook user, you are also subject to Facebook’s privacy policy. Please check your Facebook account privacy settings for further information.

Collecting Information About You  
We collect different types of information about App users for four main reasons:  
1\. To personalise the content of the App for individual users.  
2\. To help us to monitor and improve the App.  
3\. To advertise on the App.  
4\. With user consent, to market services to individual users.

 **Sharing your information with us and others**  
when you first access the App, for example by clicking on a link to a Thenigerialawyers from your Facebook newsfeed, you will be presented with a Facebook permissions page, which will advise you about the Facebook information you will be sharing with the App and other Facebook users. You can then decide whether or not to share your Facebook information by using the App. If you decide not to grant permission you will not be able to use the App.

By granting permission you will be agreeing to share your Facebook user details (including your name, profile picture, gender, networks, user ID and any other information you choose to share according to your Facebook account settings) as well as the user details of your Facebook friends, and information about your use of the App, for example, the articles you are reading.

If you choose to post content or other data on the App, for example, by commenting on an article, this can be accessed by all of your Facebook friends.

If you decide not to share information with your Facebook friends about a particular article you have accessed you can make your reading private using the ‘remove from timeline’ facility at the top of the article page.
